Shanel Beebe

Web Developer & Graphic Designer

CONTACT

Call: 647 - 778 - 2323

Email: hello@shanelbeebe.com

Visit: <u>shanelbeebe.com</u>

Github: shanelbb

LinkedIn: <u>Shanel Beebe</u>

SKILLS







HTML5

CSS3

JavaScript







React



Firebase



Accessibility



Responsive Web Design



Adobe CC

- Communication
- Problem Solving
- Adaptability
- Critical Thinking

EDUCATION

Juno College | 2019 - 2021

Web Development & JavaScript
Web Development Bootcamp

Toronto Film School | 2018

Graphic Design & Interactive Media

Ryerson University | 2005

BFA - Image Arts: Photography Studies

PROFILE

I am a frontend web developer and graphic designer who creates accessible, user-friendly applications using my knowledge of HTML, CSS, JavaScript and Adobe Creative Cloud. My experience in retail management and customer service has put me in a better position to really understand user needs to create exceptional user experiences. I love finding opportunities for personal and professional growth and I enjoy sharing my knowledge with others.

PROJECTS

Notice Board - HTML, SASS, React & Firebase

 Public notes app that allows users to leave friendly notes for other users. A React app built using a Firebase database to store user generated content.

Guess That Colour! - HTML, SASS, jQuery & API

 Interactive guessing game that asks users to guess which of four colours matches a randomly generated colour code. Built with jQuery and using an API to display color information.

Creative Agency - HTML, SASS & JavaScript

 Fully-responsive and accessible multi-page design conversion for a fictional design agency. An interactive website built using HTML5, SASS and vanilla JavaScript.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Peer Tutor | Toronto Film School | 2018

 Developed learning strategies, recommended learning resources and answered inquiries to guide them through project completion.

Store Manager | Addition Elle | 2014 - 2017

- Directed all sales, operational, and profit and loss aspects of a 12+ team member store operation.
- Lead a high performing team to surpassing a \$2 million yearly sales objective, achieving a year over year sales increase of 16%.
- Coached employees to provide exemplary customer service that provided satisfaction and inspired loyalty from every client.

Store Manager | WIND Mobile | 2009 - 2011

- Ensured profitability, customer satisfaction and cost-effective store operations in two high-volume locations.
- Managed all team member activities including hiring, development, coaching and motivating to achieve sales, profit and customer experience goals.